Finding aid for the Henry Clay Frick Papers, Series II: Correspondence, 1882-1929, undated HCFF.1.2
The Frick Collection/Frick Art Reference Library Archives
- Knubel - Kuhman (Box 50, Folder 9)
  Kronfeld, Saunders and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1913
  Kronig, J.O., 1913
  Krumbholz, T. Edmund, 1899, 1901
  Kubly, Henry, 1902
  Kuenzli, Fred, 1917
  Kühlmann, Hans von, 1913
  Kuhman, Eugene, 1905
- Kuhn, Loeb and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1902-1913 (Box 50, Folder 10-11)
- Kurth - L. Rouff (Box 50, Folder 12)
  Kurth, M., 1918
  L.A. Clark and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901-1912
  L.A. Hammersly and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1906
  L.H. Taylor and Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1891
  L.J. Phillips and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1913, 1921
  L.M. Newgass Co. [no place], 1912
  L. Rouff, Trousseaux and Layettes (Paris, France), 1900
- La Farge - Lainy (Box 51, Folder 1)
  La Farge, John, 1903-1908
  La Fontaine, Charles, 1915
  La Provence[passenger list from French mail steamer, departing New York to Havre, 4 June 1908]
  La Sarraz, Switzerland, 1911
  Labenere, Louise, 1912
  Labor World(New York, N.Y.), 1909
  Ladd, T. Gifford, 1913
  Ladenburg, Emily Stevens (Mrs. Adolf Ladenburg), 1917
  Laemmle, Carl, 1919
  Lafenetre, Henry, 1915, 1921
  Lafenetre, Justine H., 1914
  Lafferty, Robert C., 1914
  Lai-Yuan and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1917
  Laidlaw, C.E., 1885
  Lainy, Geo., 1899
- Lake - Lambing (Box 51, Folder 2)
  Lake Michigan Land Company/Lake Michigan Land Trustees (Chicago, Ill.), 1901-1903
  Lake Shore and Michigan Southern Railway Co. (Cleveland, Ohio), 1890
  Lally, John J., 1912
  Lamar, D., 1905
  Lambert, Samuel W., 1914-1915
  Lambing, M.A., 1886-1919
- Lamont - Lane (Box 51, Folder 3)
  Lamont, T.W., 1914-1915
  Lanahan, F.A., 1910
  Land Trust Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1908
  Landon, Jesse, 1912
  Landstreet, F.S., 1916
  Lane, F.H., 1893
  Lane, Gardiner M., 1907-1914
  Lane, Hugh, 1915
  Lane, James Warren, 1916
  Lane, Lee Britton, 1915
  Lane, Mary M., 1911
  Lane, W. Scott, 1889
- Langdon - Lasek (Box 51, Folder 4)
  Langdon, P.D., 1910
  Lange, A., Mrs., 1906
  Langenber, Gustave C., 1915
  Langman, C.N., 1915
  Lanier, Charles, 1915
  Lanz, John, 1901
  Lanzotti, Agostino, 1904
  Lapsly, Wm. L., 1894
  Laracy, K., 1905
  Large, S.P., 1901-1904
  Larkin, John B., 1886-1905
  Larson, C.D., 1909
  Lasek, L., 1916
- Lassaletta - Law and Order (Box 51, Folder 5)
  Lassaletta, Roe, 1921
  Latimer, Thomas M., 1910
  Latta, William J., 1911
  Lauder, George, 1889-1898
  Laughlin, Clothilde, 1906
  Laughlin, James, 1905
  Laughlin, Mary Irwin, 1905
  Laurence, John S., 1918
  Laux, James B., 1898-1908
  Laveley, Henry A., 1898-1907
  Law and Order Union of New York State (New York, N.Y.), 1912, 1917
- Law, Carl C., 1907-1917 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Lawlor - Lazear (Box 51, Folder 7)
  Lawlor, F.A., 1916
  Lawlor, Lillie, 1915
  Lawrence, [?], Mrs., 1912
  Lawrence, A.H., 1904
  Lawrence, Linnet Frick, 1917
  Lawrence, William, 1916-1917
  Laws, R.S., 1894
  Lawson, Thomas W., 1909
  Lawton, A.B., 1898
  Lawton, A.H., 1915
  Lawton, Frank J., 1910
  Lawyers' Club (New York, N.Y.), 1898-1913
  Layfield, John H., 1894
  Layton, Hudson F., 1916
  Layton, Jos. A., 1894
  Lazear and Orr (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1889-1890
- Le Gendre - Lebanon (Box 51, Folder 8)
  Le Gendre, Clarence F., 1914
  Le Page, John F., 1919
  League for the Preservation of American Independence [no place], 1919
  League of American Artists (Paris, France), 1905
  Leahy, M.C., 1913
  Leahy, P.M., 1922
  Leake, W.S., 1900
  Leary, Joseph P., Mrs., 1915
  Leasure, Anna T., 1904
  Leasure, John F., 1901, 1905
  Leasure, N.W., Mrs., 1896
  Leathers, C.J., 1902
  Leavitt, Chas. W., Jr., 1900-1916
  Lebanon Valley College (Annville, Pa.), 1909, 1916
- Ledyard - Lee, John (Box 51, Folder 9)
  Ledyard, Lewis Cass, 1907-1918
  Lee, Edward B., 1913, 1917
  Lee, Elisha, 1917
  Lee, George, 1912
  Lee, J. Bowers, 1905-1913
  Lee, J. McDonald, 1899
  Lee, John Thomas, 1916
- Lee, Kretschmar and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1905-1907 (Box 51, Folder 10-12)
- Lee, Kretschmar and Co. (continued), 1907-1912 (Box 52, Folder 1-10)
- Lee, M. - Lee, William Augustus (Box 53, Folder 1)
  Lee, M. (Miss), 1905
  Lee, Marvin, 1911
  Lee, Thomas F.F., 1916
  Lee, William Augustus, 1907-1918
- Leeds, Herbert C., 1903-1919 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Lees - Leiper (Box 53, Folder 3)
  Lees, John W., 1909
  Lehman, George M., 1909
  Leigh, Oliver H.G., 1912
  Leighton, George B., 1909
  Leiper, J.H., 1900
- Leisenring, E.B., 1886-1890 (Box 53, Folder 4-5)
- Leishman, John G.A., 1887-1916 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Leland - Leslie (Box 53, Folder 7)
  Leland, Lester, 1913
  Lemperly, Paul, 1907
  Lenander, Eva, 1898
  Lenox, John Powell, 1899
  Léon, Maurice, 1911
  Leonard, Anna P., 1909
  Leonard, Edgar W., 1918
  Leonard, Mattie, 1924
  Lepied, Amédée, 1916
  Lepper, George H., 1909, 1916
  Leslie, A.H., 1902
  Leslie, Frank, 1908
- Leslie's - Lewin (Box 53, Folder 8)
  Leslie's Illustrated Weekly(New York, N.Y.), 1912-1919
  Letsche, J.H., 1904
  Letts, Gerald A., 1913
  Levasseur, E., 1898
  Leveen and Company Tailors (Boston, Mass.), 1906
  Levering, Albert M., 1910
  Levin, Leonard S., 1909-1910
  Levy, Florence N., 1906, 1911
  Levy, J. Leonard, 1902-1904
  Levy, Jefferson M., 1914
  Lewin, Jeffroy J., 1914
- Lewis - Liebrecht (Box 53, Folder 9)
  Lewis and Simmons, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1912, 1917
  Lewis and Valentine Company Landscape Contractors (Roslyn, N.Y.), 1919
  Lewis, Bernard W., 1913
  Lewis, Frank C., 1913
  Lewis, H.H., 1912
  Lewis Homes Company (New York, N.Y.), 1922
  Lewis, O.F., 1909
  Lewisohn, Adolph, 1912-1918
  Libby, Frederick J., 1909
  Libby, L.E., 1912-1915
  Liebert, Gaston, 1917
  Liberty Loan Committee (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1918
  Lido Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1914-1915
  Liebrecht, F., 1890
- Liggett - Linde (Box 53, Folder 10)
  Liggett, Howard B., Jr., 1920-1921
  Littett, S.B., 1908
  Liggett, Thos., 1913
  Lillie, Lewis, 1906
  Lilley, G.C., 1915
  Lilly, Wm., 1891
  Limantour, José Y., 1910
  Lincoln, Alice N., 1908, 1911
  Lincoln, Robert T., 1903-1915
  Lincoln Safe Deposit Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1914
  Linda, W.K. Van O., 1914
  Lindabury, Richard V., 1911
  Linde, Hermann, 1896-1906
- Linden - Linton (Box 53, Folder 11)
  Linden Club [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1889
  Linden, R.J., 1887, 1891
  Linderman, R.P., 1896
  Lindlahr, Henry, 1914
  Lindsay, R.H., 1900
  Lindsay, W.J., 1909
  Lindsey, R.H., 1888
  Linehan, J.H., 1914
  Linenberg, H., 1905-1906
  Linhart, S.B., 1910
  Links (New York, N.Y.), 1918-1921
  Links Golf Club (Roslyn, N.Y.), 1921
  Linton, Horace J., 1911
- Lippincott - Little (Box 53, Folder 12)
  Lippincott, Elizabeth R., 1906
  Lippincott, Frank W., 1900
  Lippincott, Jesse H., 1887-1890
  Lippincott, Sarah E., 1902-1911
  Lippincott, Wm. H., 1887
  Lisle, T. Orchard, 1915
  Litchfield, [?] (Dr.), 1914
  Litchfield, Lawrence, 1893-1906
  Little, Alexander E., 1918
  Little and Browne, Architects (Boston, Mass.), 1902-1919
  Little, Brown and Co. (Boston, Mass.), 1912
  Little Sisters of the Poor (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1886, 1911
  Little, Wm. C., 1910
- Littleton - Lodge (Box 53, Folder 13)
  Littleton, Martin W., 1915
  Livengood, S.D., 1901
  Livingston and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1915-1916
  Livingston, Crawford, 1909-1917
  Livingston, Henry B., 1907
  Livingston, Mary Emily, 1903
  Livingstone, C.H., 1915
  Llewellyn, C.G., 1919
  Lloyd, Llewellyn W., 1910
  Lloyd, S.H., 1904
  Lloyd's Neck Club (Long Island, N.Y.), 1919
  Loar, James A., 1891-1906
  Lobing, J. Smith, 1899
  Locke, Bessie, 1908, 1911
  Lockhart, C., 1891
  Lockhart, James H., 1899-1916
  Lodge, Fred D., 1909
  Lodge, J. Alex., 1908
- Loeb - Loew's (Box 54, Folder 1)
  Loeb, Wm., Jr., 1904-1914
  Loessel, Adolph, 1906
  Loew's Incorporated (New York, N.Y), 1920-1924
- Logan - Longfellow (Box 54, Folder 2)
  Logan, Albert J., 1899-1911
  Logan, James H., 1901, 1904
  Lomax, H.J., 1914
  Lombard, Herbert Edwin, 1909
  Long, J.H., 1898
  Long, J.M., 1889
  Long, Jas. M., 1890
  Long Island Motor Parkway, Inc. [no place], 1908
  Long Island Railroad Company (New York, N.Y.), 1914-1917
  Longnecker, Ralph, 1899
  Longfellow, Alden and Harlow, Architects (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1892-1893
- Longo - Loring, Susan (Box 54, Folder 3)
  Longo, M., 1917
  Longsdorff, David, 1898
  Longworth, Nicholas, 1904
  Lonzon, Andrew, 1920
  Loo, C.T., 1916
  Lookwood, Wilton, 1905
  Loomis, A.G., 1903, 1905
  Loomis, Francis B., 1906
  Lord and Burnham Company (New York, N.Y.), 1898
  Lord, Day and Lord (New York, N.Y.), 1915
  Lord Electric Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1906, 1916
  Loree, L.F., 1902, 1918
  Lorenz, R.H., 1913, 1915
  Lorin, Jules F., 1911-1912
  Loring, Augustus Peabody, 1908-1911
  Loring, Susan M., 1908
- Loring, William Caleb, 1906-1909 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles - Love (Box 54, Folder 5)
  Los Angeles Examiner(Los Angeles, Cal.), 1909
  Lott, Sallie Frick, 1887-1914
  Lotus Magazine(New York, N.Y.), 1916, 1919
  Louch, Augustine and Co. (Seattle, Wa.), 1903
  Loughran, M.A., 1914
  Love, Bell, 1909
  Love, O.S., 1901
- Lovejoy, Francis T.F., 1897-1914 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Lovett - Luke (Box 54, Folder 7)
  Lovett, R.S., 1908-1911
  Low, Will H., 1904
  Lowe, James T., 1905
  Lowell, Francis C., 1910
  Lucas, F.C., Mrs., 1912
  Lucas, [Frederic A.], 1911
  Lucile, Ltd. [no place], 1912
  Lufkin, Wilfred W., 1918
  Luke, Arthur F., 1901
  Luke, Fannie Leighton (Mrs. Otis H. Luke), 1905
- Lull, Robert D., 1912-1914 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Lunderstadt - Lydig (Box 54, Folder 9)
  Lunderstadt, Henry, 1918
  Lunt, Alfred E., 1913
  Lunt, Edw. C., 1900
  Luther, F.S., 1912
  Lutz, T.C., 1912
  Lwoff-Parlaghy, Princess, 1917
  Lydig, Philip M., 1915
  Lydig, Rita (Mrs. Philip Lydig), 1918
- Lynch, Charles - Lynch, Mary (Box 54, Folder 10)
  Lynch, Charles McK., 1915-1920
  Lynch, Clay F., 1915
  Lynch, Julia M., 1899-1902
  Lynch, M., 1904-1905
  Lynch, Mary, 1897-1898
  Lynch, Mary A., 1906
- Lynch, Thomas, 1885-1887 (Box 54, Folder 11-12)
- Lynch, Thomas (continued), 1888-1911 (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
- Lynch, W.A. - Lytle (Box 55, Folder 3)
  Lynch, W.A., 1902
  Lynch, William R., 1912
  Lynne, William C., 1903
  Lyon, Cornelia A., 1904
  Lyon, J.D., 1899, 1903
  Lyon, John Denniston, 1888
  Lyon, Walter, 1902
  Lytle, R.F., 1896
- M.A. Hanna and Co. - M. Welte and Sons (Box 55, Folder 4)
  M.A. Hanna and Co. (Cleveland, Ohio), 1890-1902
  M.C.D. Borden and Sons (New York, N.Y.), 1912
  M.F. Augustin and Son (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1899
  M. Guggenheim's Sons (New York, N.Y.), 1899
  M. Welte and Sons (New York, N.Y.), 1902-1917
- M. Knoedler and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1895-1919 (Box 55, Folder 5-12)
- Maack - MacDonald, Arthur (Box 55, Folder 13)
  Maack, A., 1910
  MacAfee, Dwight R., 1915
  MacBurney, Marie, 1906
  MacChesney, Clara T., 1919
  MacClure and Spahr [no place], 1910
  MacConn, Townsend, 1914
  MacDonald, Arthur, 1914-1919
- MacDonald, Charles Blair, 1906-1918 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- MacDonald, Herman - MacGarr (Box 56, Folder 2)
  MacDonald, Herman A., 1913-1917
  MacDonald, Peter, 1919
  MacDowell, William G., 1906, 1908
  Mace, Ernest, 1917
  Macfarlane, Eliza, 1900
  MacGarr, Katherine Llewellyn, 1909-1918
- MacGregor - Magee, John (Box 56, Folder 3)
  MacGregor, John, 1915
  MacKay, Donald, II, 1918
  Mackey, W.C., 1900
  Macknight, Dodge, 1908
  Maclaurin, Richard C., 1911
  MacRae, Thomas H., 1913
  Macrum, Mary F., 1899
  Macy, Annie S[ullivan], 1911
  Madigan, P.F., 1907
  Madlung and Eidman (Chicago, Ill.), 1906
  Madrazo, Ricardo de, 1909-1913
  Maeder Property [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1918
  Magee, C.L., 1897
  Magee, Christoper L., no year
  Magee, Edyth I., 1907
  Magee, J.F., 1909
  Magee, John, 1919
- Magee, W.C., 1893-1903 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Magee, William - Mahoney (Box 56, Folder 5)
  Magee, William A., 1909-1912
  Maher, Anne M., 1922
  Maher, N.D., 1917-1918
  Mahon, Myra Overholt, 1919
  Mahoney, J.J., Mrs., 1914
  Mahoney, Jeremiah, 1908
- Main - Manhattan (Box 56, Folder 6)
  Main and Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1919
  Major, E.M., 1911
  Mall, L.R., Mrs., 1919
  Mallet-Prevost, Severo, 1907-1908
  Malone, S., 1920
  Maloy, F.B., 1897-1914
  Maloy, Mary, 1898-1899
  Mamaux, John J., 1913
  Manby, Irene G., 1909
  Manchester and Prentis (Detroit, Mich.), 1903
  Manchester, Dorset and Granville (Proctor, Vt.), 1917
  Manchester Yacht Club [no place], 1906
  Manhattan Opera House [New York, N.Y.], 1906
  Manhattan Life Insurance Co. of New York (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1899
  Manhattan Press Clipping Bureau (New York, N.Y.), 1917
  Manhattan Trust Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1909
- Mann - Marine (Box 56, Folder 7)
  Mann, E.D., 1899
  Mann, Isaac T., 1912-1916
  Mann, Ralph H., 1911
  Mann, W.D., 1907
  Mannheimer, Leo, 1917
  Manning, Daniel, 1922
  Manning, John B., 1906
  Manning, W.T., 1902, 1907
  Mansfield, E.S., 1909
  Mansfield, Howard, 1915-1916
  Mansfield, Howard, Mrs., 1906
  Manson, W.O., 1921
  Manufacturers' News(Chicago, Ill.), 1916
  Manufacturers Record(Baltimore, Md.), 1903, 1906
  Marble Workers' Union No. 15 (Allegheny, Pa.), 1902
  Marbury, Elizabeth, 1915
  Marc Eidlitz and Son, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1920
  Marine Insurance Co., Ltd. [various places], 1900-1920
- Maris - Marshall (Box 56, Folder 8)
  Maris, Herbert L., 1908
  Mark Cross Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1912
  Markle, John, 1916
  Markle, Mary A., 1890
  Marks, Alfred C., 1915
  Marlborough Club (London, England), 1914
  Marsh, Benjamin C., 1909
  Marsh, Daniel L., 1909
  Marsh, F.L., 1902-1911
  Marsh, F.L., Mrs., 1896
  Marsh, F.M., 1908
  Marshall, Alexander, 1922
  Marshall, C.S., 1900-1909
  Marshall, Frances W., 1911
  Marshall, G.C., 1901
  Marshall, Harry, 1899
  Marshall, Josephine Lenox (Mrs. Charles H. Marshall), 1915
  Marshall, M.A., 1896
  Marshall, Stuart B., 1918
- Martin - Martyn (Box 56, Folder 9)
  Martin, A.R., 1900
  Martin and Martin (New York, N.Y.), 1898, 1900
  Martin, E.J., 1900-1911
  Martin, Easthope, 1914-1916
  Martin, Eben W., 1903
  Martin, Edw'd., 1897-1898
  Martin, G.W., 1905
  Martin, Georges, 1897, 1900
  Martin, Lucy de Grasse, 1901
  Martin, Percy, 1921, 1923
  Martin, R.S., 1897
  Martin, T.P., Jr., 1915
  Martin, W.R., 1911
  Martin, Wm., 1900-1902
  Martinez, Delores, 1915
  Martiny, Philip, 1917
  Martyn, Mary A., 1914
- Marvel - Mather, Frank (Box 56, Folder 10)
  Marvel, William D., 1916
  Marvey, Nelly, 1913
  Marwick, James, 1916
  M[ary] Agatha, Sister, 1894
  Masaoka, Naoichi, 1912
  Mashey, Elizabeth J., 1903
  Mason, Alfred Bishop, 1914
  Mason, Arthur, 1907
  Mason, H.C., 1909
  Mason, Joseph D., 1916
  Mason, L.W., 1901
  Mason, Maud M., 1914
  Mason, O.H.L., 1916
  Mason, W.G., 1908-1909
  Mason, William G., 1915
  Mason, W.L., Mrs., 1924
  Massachusetts Forestry Association [no place], 1912
  Massachusetts Highway Commission (Boston, Mass.), 1909-1914
  Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Cambridge, Mass.), 1925
  Massachusetts Police Association [no place], 1906
  Massachusetts Society of Sex Education [no place], 1914
  Massie, W.W., Mrs., 1900
  Mather, Frank Jewett, 1915
- Mather, Samuel, 1896-1917 (Box 56, Folder 11-12)
- Mather, Wm. - May (Box 57, Folder 1)
  Mather, Wm. G., 1902
  Mattesa[?], J.R., 1915
  Matthews Bro's Manufacturing Co. (Milwaukee, Wis.), 1898, 1902
  Matthews, John C., 1905
  Matthews, Nathan, 1909-1914
  Matthews, William H., 1908-1910
  Maude, F.C., 1907
  Mauk, Chas. C., 1897
  Maurer, G.C., 1913
  Mauro, Philip, 1900
  Maury, C.A., 1905
  Max Schamberg and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1899
  Maxon, W.D., 1897-1898
  Maxwell, David B., 1917
  May, A.S., 1910
  May, De Courcy, 1903-1908
- Mayer - McCabe (Box 57, Folder 2)
  Mayer, W.W., 1909
  Maylender, Louis K., 1906
  Maynard, Karl, 1915
  Maynard, Martha, 1906
  Mayor (New York, N.Y.), undated
  Mayr, George, 1906
  McAdoo, W.A., 1917-1918
  McAllister, C.T., 1915
  McAllister, J.R., 1902-1908
  McAlpin, B.B., 1916
  McAlpin, Geo. S., 1906, 1908
  McAlpin, Henry, 1918-1919
  McBride, L., 1897, 1908
  McCabe, Charles C., 1903
  McCabe, Joseph, 1914
- McCague - McCall (Box 57, Folder 3)
  McCague, George E., 1891-1915
  McCain, George Nox, 1899-1913
  McCain, Mary V.O., 1911-1912
  McCall, Samuel Walker, 1917
- McCallam - McConway (Box 57, Folder 4)
  McCallam, Geo. W., 1898
  McCandless, Collingwood and Alexander (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1923
  McCandless, Geo. W., 1913
  McCargo, Grant, 1916
  McCarthy, P.B., 1916
  McCarty, Chas. H., 1908
  McCarty, Lyman, [1903?]
  McClaren, John W., 1908
  McClellan, Jesse, 1907
  McClintic, H.H., Mrs., 1918
  McClintock, Oliver, 1906-1914
  McClure's Magazine(New York, N.Y.), 1908
  McClure, Thos. G., 1897, [1903?]
  McClurg, J.F., 1920
  McCombs, C.B., 1915
  McConnell, Annie, 1916
  McConnell, Edward, 1909
  McConnell, N., 1900
  McConway, Wm., 1901-1902
- McCook, John J., 1899-1904 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- McCook, Katherine - McCrea, Archibald (Box 57, Folder 6)
  McCook, Katherine, 1907-1908
  McCook, Mary, 1901
  McCook, Willis F., 1897-1913
  McCord, Joseph A., 1907
  McCormack, Ira A., 1915
  McCormick, Cyrus H., 1907
  McCormick, P.H., 1924
  McCormick, S.B., 1906
  McCormick, Vance C., 1900-1901
  McCracken, Anna Marshall, 1906
  McCracken, Mary L., 1906
  McCrady Brothers Co. (Braddock, Pa.), 1915
  McRea, Archibald M., 1910
- McCrea, James, 1896-1920 (Box 57, Folder 7-9)
- McCreary - McDowell (Box 57, Folder 10)
  McCreary, Harry, 1904, 1908
  McCreery and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1904, 1906
  McCrory, W.J., 1900
  McCuen, Herbert F., 1924
  McCullough, Edmd. H., 1897
  McCurdy-Brainard Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1917
  McCurdy, [George O.?], 1886
  McCutcheon, W.A., 1899
  McCutcheon, W.J., 1901
  McDonald, James A., 1919
  McDonald, John F., 1907
  McDonnell, Lena J., 1911
  McDowell, William Osborn, 1917-1918
- McEldowney, H.C., 1902-1911 (Box 57, Folder 11-12)
- McEldowney, H.C. (continued), 1912-1924 (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
- McElfresh, F.E., 1912 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- McElroy, F.W., [1903?]-1915, undated (Box 58, Folder 5-6)
- McElroy, Lily A. (Mrs. F.W. McElroy), 1916-1917 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- McElroy, Samuel - McHugh (Box 58, Folder 8)
  McElroy, Samuel, 1898
  McElroy, W.K., 1920
  McErry, Agnes G., 1900
  McFadden, John H., 1917, 1919
  McFarlane, Geo. L., 1901
  McFee, B., 1894
  McGeagh, E.J., Mrs., 1903
  McGee, H.E., 1925
  McGee, W.L., 1910
  McGeorge, James M., 1904
  McGillick, F.E., 1917
  McGonigal, Edward J., 1908-1909
  McGowan, J.P., 1897-1898
  McGowan, Margaret, 1904
  McGuire, William J., 1906, 1918
  McGurk, Jonce I., 1914-1915
  McHugh, Michael J., 1911-1912
- McIlvain - McIntyre (Box 58, Folder 9)
  McIlvain, E.M., 1902
  McIlvaine, E.S., 1918
  McIlvaine, J.H., 1902-1911
  McIntire, A.W., 1899
  McIntyre, Wm. H., 1902-1903
- McKahan - McKim (Box 58, Folder 10)
  McKahan, John D., 1906
  McKallip, Charles C., 1918-1919
  McKean, James S., no year
  McKee, Anne Patrick, 1905
  McKee, F.W., 1897
  McKee, I.D., 1897
  McKee, Logan, 1906
  McKee, Mary Stuart, 1899
  McKee, N.M., 1903
  McKee, Thomas M., 1909-1913
  McKelvey, F.B., 1921-1922
  McKelvy, H.R., 1897
  McKelvy, W.A., Mrs., 1915
  McKenna, Chas. F., 1903
  McKenzie, M., 1912
  McKim, C.F., 1906
- McKinley - McNamara Brothers (Box 58, Folder 11)
  McKinley Birthplace Memorial Association (Niles, Ohio), 1915, 1917
  McKinley, William, 1891-1900
  McKinney, J.L., 1894
  McKinney, W.N., 1899
  McKnight, Wharton, 1898
  McLain, Jno. A., 1897
  McLean, C.B., 1897
  McLean, J.R., 1905
  McLenahan, Cordelia Marguerite, 1916
  McLenahan, Thomas Morrow, 1916
  McManigal, Herbert, 1900
  McManus, William H., 1901
  McMaster, Jennie K., 1908
  McMaster, Natalie, 1909
  McMicken, Andrew, 1898
  McMillan, E.H. (Mrs. John McMillan), 1904
  McMorran, Charles Wesley, 1912-1917, undated
  McMunn, S.W., 1909
  McMurran, Charles W., 1904, 1908
  McNair, Chas. A., 1880
  McNamara Brothers, 1912
- McNamara, Edward J., 1914-1920 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- McNanamy - McWhinney (Box 58, Folder 13)
  McNanamy, W.J., 1904
  McNeal, Mary, 1909
  McNeir, Wm., 1910
  McNulty Bros. (Chicago, Ill.), 1902
  McPherson, J.D., 1910
  McPherson, James, 1918
  McPherson, Logan G., 1905
  McRae, A.K., 1917
  McSwigan, Charles H., 1903-1915
  McTague, Pat, 1899
  McTerney, H.C., 1899
  McTighe, Thos. J., 1903
  McVay, C.B., 1899
  McVickar, Gaillard Realty Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1907
  McWhinney, Robert, 1908-1911
  McWhinney, Robert, Mrs., 1910
- Meagher - Mellen (Box 59, Folder 1)
  Meagher, M.T., 1913
  Meakin, Wm. Paley, 1914
  Meanor, Geo. B., 1901
  Mechling, W.W., 1910
  Meehan, A.E., Mrs., 1920
  Meehan Detective Agency (New York, N.Y.), 1914
  Meersman, H., 1909-1914 See also: Bane and Hill (New York, N.Y)
  Meert, V.E., 1910
  Megrew, George, 1901, 1914
  Melba, Nellie, 1918
  Melchers, Gari, 1918
  Meldrum, James, 1911
  Melillo and C. (Naples, Italy), 1916
  Mellen, C.S., 1910
- Mellon, Andrew W., 1883-1919 (Box 59, Folder 2-5)
- Mellon, James R., 1898-1907 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Mellon National Bank (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902-1922 (Box 59, Folder 7-8)
- Mellon, Nora M., 1911 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Mellon, R.B., 1902-1919 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Mellon, W.L. - Mercantile Trust and Deposit (Box 59, Folder 11)
  Mellon, W.L., 1906, 1915
  Mellon, Wm. P., 1907
  Mellor, C.C., 1899
  Melrose, Paul, 1915
  Meneely Bell Co. (Troy, N.Y.), 1907
  Menken, Percival S., 1903
  Menken, S. Stanwood, 1915
  Men's Singing Club (Beverly, Mass.), 1915, 1919
  Menzies, Helta Graham, 1914
  Mercantile National Bank (Salem, Mass.), 1903
  Mercantile Safe Deposit Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1904-1912
  Mercantile Trust and Deposit Co. (Baltimore, Md.), 1915
- Mercantile Trust Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1899-1902 (Box 59, Folder 12-14)
- Mercantile Trust Co. (continued), 1903-1908 (Box 60, Folder 1-10)
- Mercantile Trust Co. (continued), 1909-1911 (Box 61, Folder 1-8)
- Mercedes - Merrill (Box 61, Folder 9)
  Mercedes Automobile Headquarters (New York, N.Y.), 1909
  Mercer, George, 1918
  Mercer, J.C., 1902
  Merchant Marine League of the United States (Cleveland, Ohio), 1909
  Merchants' Association of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1918
  Merchants Exchange National Bank (New York, N.Y.), 1901
  Merchants' Loan and Trust Co. (Chicago, Ill.), 1912
  Merchants National Bank (Salem, Mass.), 1903
  Mercur, William H., 1904, 1906
  Mercy Hospital (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1896-1925
  Meredith, J. Morris, 1903
  Meredith, William F., 1919
  Merigold, W.A., 1911
  Merrill, Anna Kinsman, 1900
  Merrill, Bradford, 1912
  Merrill, C.L., 1904
  Merrill, E.C., 1899
  Merrill, J.L. Woods, 1909
  Merrill, Keith, 1919
  Merrill, Mary E. Ruth, 1910
  Merrill, Wm. Hutchinson, 1900
- Merriman - Metropolitan Life (Box 62, Folder 1)
  Merriman, M.A. Mrs., 1906
  Mersereau, Christy, 1913-1914
  Mershon, Edward C., 1912
  Meserve, [?], 1911
  Messayer, R.D., 1916
  Messler, Eugene L., 1903
  Metcalf, Esther Pierce (Mrs. Stephen O. Metcalf), 1907
  Methodist Episcopal Church (South Essex, Mass.), 1911
  Metropolitan Church Association (Chicago, Ill.), 1916
  Metropolitan Club (New York, N.Y.), 1902-1921
  Metropolitan Club (Washington, D.C.), 1903-1904
  Metropolitan Coal Co. (Boston, Mass.), 1900
  Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1899
- Metropolitan Museum of Art (New York, N.Y.), 1898-1919 (Box 62, Folder 2-4)
- Metropolitan Opera - Metzger (Box 62, Folder 5)
  Metropolitan Opera and Real Estate Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1907-1923
  Metropolitan Trust Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1916-1919
  Mettler, F.W., 1904
  Metz, C.J., 1902
  Metz, Herman A., 1909
  Metzgar, G.C., 1912
  Metzger, Chas. W., 1896
- Meyer - Millar (Box 62, Folder 6)
  Meyer, Eugene, Jr., 1919
  Meyer, George von L., 1907
  Meyer, Luis M., 1897
  Mezger, A., 1916
  Michael, William H., 1901
  Michaelis and Rohman (New York, N.Y.), 1900
  Michelland, Jno. E., 1919
  Midland Valley Railroad Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1914-1915
  Millard Construction Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1908
  Milligan, J.L., 1901